NOAM ACKERMAN

Frontend developer.

Phone: +972505954084

Email: developer.noam@gmail.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/noam-ackerman/

Summary

I am Noam Ackerman, I've started my coding journey studying at "SheCodes USA". In my previous position I worked as a Frontend developer at "Nosto Solutions" (working with React, JavaScript, CSS, etc...).

Currently I'm doing freelance projects as a developer. I'm also a musician (singer, songwriter, instrumentalist and music producer) and a visual artist.

I am curious, passionate and diligent, with a strong will power. I enjoy challenges and solving problems.

I value a healthy, productive and respectful communication.

Skills

- Proficient with various technologies & languages such as ReactJS, JavaScript, TypeScript, CSS, Sass, HTML, Git, Jest, Firebase, Responsive development
- Proficient with various software tools such as VS codes, Figma, Slack, Jira, Photoshop, Illustrator, Ableton
- Team player, fast learner, problem solver and highly creative

Experience

2023 - Present - Freelancer Full Stack Developer at "PlayTracker"

Playtracker is a multi-platform gaming destination, that grabs data from the user's linked gaming platforms and displays all the games, achievements, playtime and other available stats in one place. In my unique role I'm carrying out an extensive research of multiple gaming platforms & games APIs in order to form solutions related to players data and features implementations.

2021 - 2023 - Frontend Developer at "Nosto Solutions" an Ecommerce Experience Platform

- · Creating dynamic, interactive and responsive interfaces used by thousands of costumers daily
- · Fullfiling hundreds of Jira tickets and taking ownership of features from figma to production
- · Investigating different site environments of merchants, creating solutions and fixing bugs
- Developing mockups and wireframes for UI and optimized UX
- Initiating and leading a new team workflow guidelines and creating documents to increase team productivity and optimize project management efficiency
- Providing technical guidance to merchants

2021 - 2023 - Updating my portfolio with projects I've built using several languages and technologies Public at – www.noamackerman.com

Highlighted projects:

- Calendar-app (Demo | Repo) I'm currently building with React, TypeScript, Sass, React-hook-form library,
 Date-fns, MUI and Firebase for auth and database.
- Post Your Thought (Demo | Repo) A social media platform I've designed and built with React, JSX, JS,
 CSS modules and Firebase integration for Auth, Database and Storage. Authenticated users can set up their profile, post their thoughts, navigate through users profile pages and the homepage feeds.

Education

- 2023 Online courses for Advanced React, for TypeScript and for NodeJS.
- 2021 SheCodes USA Front-end, React and responsive web development Intensive studies of all major technologies, languages and softwares related to frontend development. During the studies we were faced with multiple exercises, assignments and real-time projects.
- 2018 2019 Music production and sound design studies at "Catalyst music" (formerly "dbs music").
- Graduated with honor 12 years of formal education and received high school diploma.

Languages

Hebrew - Native English - Fluent German - A2

Citizenships

Israeli EU Citizenship